Guide to the Gertrude Stein and Alice B. Toklas Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings of Gertrude Stein, 1894-1947; Series I; 39; (94 boxes)
  - GERTRUDE STEIN BIBLIOGRAPH
    - Portrait of Prince B. D.
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1913] (Box 67, Folder 1205)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Portraits and Prayers
      - Dedication, holograph manuscript (2 drafts), [1934] (Box 67, Folder 1206)
      - Clippings, 1934-35 (Box 67, Folder 1207-1208)
    - Possessive case
      - Manuscript notebook v. 1, [1915] (Box 68, Folder 1209)
        Also contains: Notice Oscar Wilde
      - Manuscript notebook v. 2, [1915] (Box 68, Folder 1210)
      - Manuscript notebook v. 3, [1915] (Box 68, Folder 1211)
        Also contains: Mrs. Whitehead
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, corrected, 1915 (Box 68, Folder 1212)
    - Practice in orations
      See: Practice of oratory
    - Practice of oratory
      - Manuscript notebook, [1923] (Box 68, Folder 1213)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1923 (Box 68, Folder 1214)
    - Praises
      - Holograph manuscript, [1923] (Box 68, Folder 1215)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1216)
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), 1923 (Box 68, Folder 1217)
    - Precepts
      - Holograph manuscript, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1218)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1219)
    - Preciosilla
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913]
        In: Irma
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Program for performance of musical setting by Virgil Thomson
        See: Susie Asado
    - The Present
      Also contains: Italy, The Liberty loan, Sacred fountain of Bellows, Say it again, AND Postal cards
      - Manuscript notebook, [1919]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1220)
        Also contains: J. R.
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1919 (Box 68, Folder 1221)
    - Prim roses
      - Holograph manuscript, [1918] (Box 68, Folder 1222)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copies (2 versions), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1223)
      - Typescript carbon copy, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1224)
    - Procession
      - Manuscript notebook, [1923] (Box 68, Folder 1225)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copies (2 versions), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1226)
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1227)
      - Printed version, Programme, 1935 Jun (Box 68, Folder 1228)
    - Prothalamium
      - Holograph manuscript, [1939] (Box 68, Folder 1229)
    - Prudence caution and foresight. A Story of Avignon
      - Manuscript notebook, [1922] (Box 68, Folder 1230)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), corrected, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1231)
    - The Psychology of Nations
      - Holograph manuscript, [1920] (Box 68, Folder 1232)
      - Typescript, n.d.
    - Publishers
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913] (Box 68, Folder 1233)
        Also contains: England
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Purmann
      - Holograph manuscript, [1908-12] (Box 68, Folder 1234)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1235)
    - Puzzled America
      See: Review of Puzzled America
    - Q.E.D.
      "Notes and drafts"
      See: Series V. Personal Papers, Box 139, folder 3274
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1903] (Box 69, Folder 1236-1237)
        [sent by ABT in 1947 to Carl Van Vechten who gave them to Yale in 1951]
      - Typescript, corrected, [1947] (Box 69, Folder 1238)
        [made by ABT in 1947 and sent to Carl Van Vechten who gave it to Yale in 1951]
    - Que sont nos contemporaines?
      - Lecture announcement, 1945 Dec 21 (Box 69, Folder 1239)
    - Qu'est-ce je pense de la France
      - Holograph manuscript, [1934] (Box 69, Folder 1240)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1241)
      - Printed version, Intrasigeant, 1934 Jan 6 (Box 69, Folder 1242)
        See also: Oversize, Box 168, folder 4320
    - Quod Erat Demonstratum
      See: Q.E.D.
    - R. D. in unrecreation
      See: Portrait of Prince B. D.
    - A Radical expert
    - Raoul Dufy
      See: One must meditate about pleasure
    - Read a new currant
      - Manuscript notebook, [1921]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1243)
    - Readings
      - Manuscript notebook, [1921]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d.
        In: Courting
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1244)
    - Realism in novels
      - Holograph manuscript, [1943] (Box 69, Folder 1245)
      - Manuscript notebook, [1943] (Box 69, Folder 1246)
        Also contains: Look and long
    - Red Faces
      - Manuscript notebook, [1918]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1918 (Box 69, Folder 1247)
      - Typescript copy, n.d.
    - Reflection on happy married life
      See: Didn't Nelly and Lily love you
    - Reflections on the Atomic Bomb
      See: The Atomic Bomb
    - Regular regularly in narrative
      - Manuscript notebooks (v. 1-5), [1927] (Box 69, Folder 1248-1250)
      - Manuscript notebook v. 6, [1927]
        In: Four saints in three acts
    - Relief work in France
      - Holograph manuscript, [1917] (Box 69, Folder 1251)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1919 (Box 69, Folder 1252)
      - Printed version, Life, 1917 Dec 27 (Box 69, Folder 1253)
    - Relieve
      - Manuscript notebook, [1927]
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1254)
    - Reread another
      - Holograph manuscript, [1921] (Box 69, Folder 1255)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Responsibilities
    - Le Retour à Paris
      See: We are back in Paris
    - The Return
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1929] (Box 69, Folder 1256)
      - Typescript copy, 1930 (Box 69, Folder 1257)
    - The Revery of the Zionist
      - Holograph manuscript, [1920] (Box 69, Folder 1258)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, corrected, 1920 (Box 69, Folder 1259)
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1260)
      - Typescript carbon copy, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1261)
    - Review of Oscar Wilde discovers America
      [By Lloyd Lewis and Henry Justin Smith]
      - Manuscript notebook, [1936]
      - Printed version, Chicago Daily Tribune, 1936 Aug 8 (Box 70, Folder 1262)
        See also: Oversize, Box 168, folder 4321
    - Review of Puzzled America by Sherwood Anderson
      - Holograph manuscript, [1935] (Box 70, Folder 1263)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1264)
      - Printed version, Chicago Daily Tribune, 1935 May 4
        See: Oversize, Box 168, folder 4322
    - Review of Roosevelt and His America by Bernard Faÿ
      - Printed version, Kansas City Star, 1934 Jan 20 (Box 70, Folder 1265)
    - Review of A Storyteller's Story by Sherwood Anderson
      - Holograph manuscript, [1925] (Box 70, Folder 1266)
      - Typescript copies (2 versions), n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1267)
      - Printed version, Ex Libris, 1925 Mar (Box 70, Folder 1268)
      - Excerpt from printed version, Ex Libris, [various sources], 1925 Mar (Box 70, Folder 1269)
    - Review of Three Stories and Ten Stories
      [By Ernest Hemingway]
      - Printed version, Chicago Tribune - European Edition, 1923 Nov 27
        See: Oversize, Box 168, folder 4323
    - Review of Troubador: An Autobiography by Alfred Kreymborg
      - Notes
      - Printed version, [various sources], n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1270)
    - Review of Yesterday's Burdens by Robert Coates
      - Holograph manuscript, [1931] (Box 70, Folder 1271)
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1272)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, 1933 (Box 70, Folder 1273)
      - Excerpts from printed version, 1934 (Box 70, Folder 1274)
    - Riba-Rovira
    - Rich and poor in England
      - Holograph manuscript, [1920] (Box 70, Folder 1275)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1276)
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1920 (Box 70, Folder 1277)
    - Rich and poor in English
      See: Rich and poor in England
    - Rich in the city
      - Manuscript notebook, [1918]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1278)
      - Typescript carbon copy, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1279)
    - Roché
      - Holograph manuscript, [1908-12] (Box 70, Folder 1280)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Rooms
    - Rue de Rennes
      - Holograph manuscript, [1908-12] (Box 70, Folder 1281)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copies (2 versions), corrected, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1282)
    - Russell
      - Holograph manuscript, [1908-12] (Box 70, Folder 1283)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1284)
      - Typescript carbon copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1285)
    - Rutherford B. Hayes and Grant
      See: Grant or Rutherford B. Hayes
    - Sacred Emily
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913] (Box 70, Folder 1286)
        Also contains: Tillie
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - A Saint in seven
      - Manuscript notebook, [1922] (Box 70, Folder 1287)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Advertisement (for "Un Saint en Sept"), Midi à Midi, publié par orbes, 1930 Feb
        See: Oversize, Box 168, folder 4324
    - Saints and singing. A play
      - Manuscript notebook v. 1, [1922] (Box 70, Folder 1288)
      - Manuscript notebook v. 2 (loose pages with wrapper), [1922] (Box 70, Folder 1289)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Saving the sentence
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929]
        In: Sentences and paragraphs
      - Proof of pages [13]-14 from How to Write, n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1290)
    - Say it with flowers. A play at tragedy
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1931] (Box 70, Folder 1291)
    - Scenery
      - Holograph manuscript, [1920] (Box 70, Folder 1292)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1920 (Box 70, Folder 1293)
    - Scenery and George Washington
    - Scenes, Actions and disposition of relations...
      See: Scenes in relation
    - Scenes in relation
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913] (Box 70, Folder 1294)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Scenes from the door
      - Holograph manuscript, [1919] (Box 70, Folder 1295)
      - Typescript, n.d.
    - Selected poems
      Contents: Amaryllis or The prettiest legs; An incident; What is this; A Lesson for baby; A Radical expert; America; Your own; Let us talk about waxing; In this way, kissing; Can you imitate disaster; In the same poem; An elegant escape; Can you climb in little things; We cannot; Why cannot you speak in pieces; AND Making sense
      - Manuscript notebook, [1918] (Box 70, Folder 1296)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copies (2 versions), n.d. (Box 70, Folder 1297)
      - Typescript carbon, corrected, 1918 (Box 70, Folder 1298)
    - A Sentence
      See: Christian Bérard
    - The Sentence
      See: Sentences
    - Sentences
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1928-29] (Box 71, Folder 1299-1302)
        Also contains (v. 5): Basket AND Five words in a line
    - Sentences and paragraphs
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929] (Box 71, Folder 1303)
        Also contains: Saving the sentence
    - Separated
      - Manuscript notebook, [1921]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1304)
        Also contains: Attacks
      - Typescript carbon copies (3), n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1305)
    - Series [I-XL]
      - Manuscript notebook, [1914] (Box 71, Folder 1306)
      - Typescript corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1307)
      - Typescript carbon copies (3), corrected, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1308)
    - She said, a poem
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929]
    - Sherwood's sweetness
      - Manuscript notebook, [1941] (Box 71, Folder 1309)
    - Short sentences a play
      - Manuscript notebook, [1932] (Box 71, Folder 1310)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1311)
    - Simon
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913] (Box 71, Folder 1312)
        Also contains: Bee time vine
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), corrected, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1313)
    - Simons a bouquet, a play
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913] (Box 71, Folder 1314)
      - Typescript, n.d.
        See also: Their wills. A Bouquet.
    - Singing to a musician
      - Manuscript notebook, [1921]
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - A Singular addition...
      [Full title: A Singular addition. A sequel to An Instant answer or One hundred prominent men]
      - Manuscript notebook, [1922] (Box 71, Folder 1315)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 1316)
    - Sir Francis Rose [1934]
      See: Introduction to the catalogue of an exhibition in London of Francis Rose's pictures
    - Sir Francis Rose [1932]
      See: Waiting for what
    - A Sister's revenge
      - Notes
    - Sitwell Edith Sitwell
      - Holograph manuscript, [1925] (Box 72, Folder 1317)
      - Typescript, n.d.
    - A Sonatina followed by another...
      [Full title: A Sonatina followed by another. Dedicated by request to D. D.]
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1921] (Box 72, Folder 1318-1321)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (3), corrected (2 copies incomplete), n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1322)
    - Sonnets that please
      - Holograph manuscript, [1921] (Box 72, Folder 1323)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon, corrected, 1921 (Box 72, Folder 1324)
    - Stanzas in meditation
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1932] (Box 72, Folder 1325-1330)
        Volume 4 has 1 leaf of notes laid in
      - Typescript copies (2), corrected, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1331-1333)
      - Proof of Stanzas I-III ("Vers libre"), n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1334)
      - Printed version of stanzas I-III, [unidentified source], with notes on verso, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1335)
      - Printed version of Stanza 69, Orbes (with parallel French translation by Marcel Duchamp), 1932-33 (Box 73, Folder 1336)
      - Printed version of Stanza LXXI (on Picabia), exhibition catalog, Paris (with parallel French translation by Marcel Duchamp), 1932 (Box 73, Folder 1337)
      - Printed version of Stanza LXXI (on Picabia), exhibition catalog, Chicago, 1936 Jan (Box 73, Folder 1338)
      - Printed version of selected stanzas, Life and Letters To-day, 1936-37 (Box 73, Folder 1339)
    - Stieglitz
      - Holograph manuscript, [1934] (Box 73, Folder 1340)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1341)
    - Still more about money
      - Manuscript notebook, [1936]
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1342)
      - Printed version, Saturday Evening Post, 1936 Jul 25 (Box 73, Folder 1343)
        See also: Oversize, Box 168, folder 4325
    - A Story
      - Holograph manuscript, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1344)
        Includes: Do you like this story, A short story, A long story made shorter AND A poem
    - The Story of a book
      - Holograph manuscript, [1933] (Box 73, Folder 1345)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 1346)
      - Printed version, Wings, 1933 Sep (Box 73, Folder 1347)
    - Storyette of H. M.
      - Typescript, n.d.
    - A Storyteller's story
      See: Review of: A Storyteller's story by Sherwood Anderson
    - Studies in Conversation
      - Manuscript notebook, [1923] (Box 73, Folder 1348)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, 1923 (Box 73, Folder 1349)
    - Study in possessives
      See: Possessive case
    - Study nature
      - Manuscript notebook, [1915]
        In: Johnny Grey
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1915 (Box 73, Folder 1350)
    - Subject-cases. The Background of a detective story
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1923] (Box 74, Folder 1351-1353)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, 1923 (Box 74, Folder 1354)
    - A Summer with Marcels
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929]
    - Sundays and Tuesdays
      See: The Winner Loses
    - Superstitions
      - Holograph manuscript (in English), [1940] (Box 74, Folder 1355)
      - Manuscript notebook (in French, includes copy in the hand of Thornton Wilder), [1940] (Box 74, Folder 1356)
      - Typescript copy (in French), corrected, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1357)
    - The Superstitions of Fred Anneday, Annday, Anday
      - Manuscript notebook, [1934] (Box 74, Folder 1358)
      - Typescript copy (incomplete), n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1359)
      - Printed version, The Nassau Lit, 1935 Dec (Box 74, Folder 1360)
    - Susan B. Anthony
      See: The Mother of us all
    - Susie Asado
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Program for performance of musical setting by Virgil Thomson, 1929 Jul 17 (Box 74, Folder 1361)
    - A Sweet tail
      - Manuscript notebook, [1913] (Box 74, Folder 1362)
        Also contains: Carnage
      - Typescript, corrected
    - Talks to Saints. Or stories of Saint Remy
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1922] (Box 74, Folder 1363)
        (v. 1 includes drafts of letters to Sherwood Anderson and Jean Cocteau)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon, corrected, 1922 (Box 74, Folder 1364)
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1365)
    - Tender Buttons
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 1366)
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1910-12] (Box 74, Folder 1367-1369)
      - Typescript, corrected
      - Advertising catalog from Claire Marie, 1914 (Box 75, Folder 1370)
      - Clippings, 1914-33 (Box 75, Folder 1371-1373)
    - Thank you
      - Holograph manuscript, [1913] (Box 75, Folder 1374)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, 1913 (Box 75, Folder 1375)
      - Typescript carbon copy, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1376)
    - Their Wills. A Bouquet.
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1928] (Box 75, Folder 1377)
      - Typescript, corrected (part: An Interlude. Simons a bouquet), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1378)
    - Then Steal
      - Holograph manuscript, [1919] (Box 75, Folder 1379)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1380)
    - They asked what I thought of the atomic bomb
      See: The Atomic bomb
    - They must be said to be ready
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929]
    - They must. Be wedded. To their wife. A play
      - Manuscript notebook, [1951] (Box 75, Folder 1381)
      - Programs for performances of "A Wedding Bouquet, London, 1937, 1938 (Box 75, Folder 1382)
      - Clippings [re: "A Wedding Bouquet"], 1937 Apr (Box 75, Folder 1383)
    - They weighed weighed-layed
      - Manuscript notebooks (Box 75, Folder 1384)
    - Things as they are
    - Think again
      - Manuscript notebook, [1921]
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), corrected, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1385)
    - Think with a minute
      - Notes
    - A Third
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1925-26?] (Box 75, Folder 1386-1387)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1388)
    - A Third day not thirsty
      - Manuscript notebook, [1918]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1389)
        Also contains: Can call us
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1918 (Box 75, Folder 1390)
    - Third Forensic
      [Theme written at Radcliffe, titled: "The Modern Jew"]
      - Holograph manuscript, 1896 Mar 7 (Box 75, Folder 1391)
    - Third historic drama
      - Manuscript notebook, [1930] (Box 75, Folder 1392)
      - [EMPTY FOLDER] (Box 75, Folder 1393)
    - This one is serious
      - Manuscript notebook, [1915] (Box 75, Folder 1394)
        Also contains: He didn't light the light (notebook and copy in the hand of ABT)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), corrected, 1915 (Box 75, Folder 1395)
    - Thoughts on American contemporary feeling
      - Holograph manuscript, [1931] (Box 76, Folder 1396)
      - Typescript copy, corrected with carbon copy, corrected, 1931 (Box 76, Folder 1397)
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 1398)
      - Printed version, Creative Art, 1932 Feb (Box 76, Folder 1399)
    - Three dishonest ones
      See: Four dishonest ones
    - Three histories
      See: Three lives
    - Three lives
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1904-05] (Box 76, Folder 1400-1405)
      - Galley proof, pp. 1-21, 68-80, corrected, [ca. 1908] (Box 76, Folder 1406)
      - Printed version (from Grafton Press, with Melanctha removed), 1909 (Box 76, Folder 1407)
      - Clipping book (includes general clippings on Gertrude Stein), 1909-14 (Box 77, Folder 1408)
      - Typescript (carbon) compilation of reviews, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 1409)
      - Typescript transcriptions of clippings, 1909-10, 1930 (Box 77, Folder 1410)
      - Clippings, 1909-33 (Box 77, Folder 1411-1412)
    - Three moral tales
      See: Moral tales of 1920 and 1921
    - Three sitting here
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1927] (Box 77, Folder 1413)
      - Printed version, Close Up, 1927 (Box 77, Folder 1414)
    - Tillie
      - Manuscript notebook, [1914]
        In: Sacred Emily
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy (with carbon copy), corrected, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 1415)
    - Title sub-title
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebook, [1930]
        In: A Grammarian
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 1416)
    - To a view
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929]
    - To call it a day
      - Notes
      - Manuscript notebook, [1924]
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, corrected, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 1417)
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 1418)
    - To do a book about alphabets and birthdays
      - Manuscript notebooks, [1940] (Box 77, Folder 1419-1422)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1423)
    - To help. In case of accident
      - Manuscript notebook, [1930] (Box 78, Folder 1424)
      - Typescript copy, 1930 (Box 78, Folder 1425)
    - To Kitty or Kate Buss
      - Manuscript notebook, [1930]
        In: Grace or Yves de Longevialle
    - To Pierre de Massot
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1426)
    - To the first bird which they heard
      - Manuscript notebook, [1929]
    - To Virgil and Eugene
      - Holograph manuscript, [1928] (Box 78, Folder 1427)
      - Typescript copies (4 versions), n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1428)
    - To-day we have a vacation
      - Manuscript notebook, [1921]
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript carbon copies (2), n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1429)
    - Tourty or Tourtebattre
      - Manuscript notebook, [1919] (Box 78, Folder 1430)
      - Typescript, n.d.
    - Trois soeurs qui sont pas soeurs
      - Manuscript notebook, [1943] (Box 78, Folder 1431)
    - A True story
    - Tubene
      - Holograph manuscript, [1914] (Box 78, Folder 1432)
      - Typescript, n.d.
      - Typescript copy, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1433)
      - Typescript carbon copy, 1914 (Box 78, Folder 1434)
    - Tuberculous larynx Early diagnosis [Medical theme]
      - Holograph manuscript, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1435)
    - Turkey and bones and eating and we liked it, a play
      - Manuscript notebook, [1916] (Box 78, Folder 1436)
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d.
    - Twenty Guineas
      - Manuscript notebook, [1937]
        In: Ida a novel
    - Twenty years with Gertrude Stein
    - Two Cubist Poems: The Peace Conference
      [i.e. More League AND Portrait of Gibb]
      - Printed version, The Oxford Magazine, 1920 May 7 (Box 78, Folder 1437)
    - Two. Gertrude Stein and her brother